<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Matt Threlfall</title>
    <link>https://www.threlfall.dev/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Matt Threlfall</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2020, Matt Threlfall; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 19:56:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.threlfall.dev/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Archaeology Game</title>
      <link>https://www.threlfall.dev/blog/digsitegame/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 19:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.threlfall.dev/blog/digsitegame/</guid>
      <description>Digsite Following LD47 I was pretty annoyed at my complete inability to use OpenGL since it caused a lot of wasted hours and on the time limit I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to slow down and learn how to use it correctly. So following this I came up with a general idea for a game I want to make in 3D. It feels like a perfect practice ground for OpenGL and a perfect way to struggle my way through 3d game development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LD47</title>
      <link>https://www.threlfall.dev/blog/ld47/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 20:12:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.threlfall.dev/blog/ld47/</guid>
      <description>Preparing LD47 Friday the 9th of October to Monday the 12th was Ludum Dare 47. A game jam where developers (try) make a game within the 3 day time period. The main event is actually the Friday-Sunday however I took part in the Jam. The theme for this Jam was &amp;ldquo;Stuck in a loop&amp;rdquo;
I had never taken part in a Ludum Dare by myself before.
Before the Jam I had decided to take part in the Jam since I was free on the weekend and thought it&amp;rsquo;d be interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://www.threlfall.dev/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.threlfall.dev/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>New site I&amp;rsquo;ve had this site for like nearly a year now and I&amp;rsquo;ve never really made any posts. Infact, I put my generated site into git but not my source, and so I lost it all when I updated my computer. So I guess I&amp;rsquo;m making it again, this time I swear I&amp;rsquo;ll save the source in git.
Me I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer with intrests in:
 lowlevel programming embedded systems machine learning cyber security game development Not web tech  A big mix of unrelated things, and it turns out I&amp;rsquo;m not good at any of them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
